{
    "id": "a47dcadfca4148d483707f8a68691c07",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was such a ………………. state of affairs that we had to laugh.",
            "description": "Comic / comical – funny, humorous, laughable",
            "answers": [
                "comic",
                "categorical",
                "brazen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6e990b5f3bfb4e39aada44b23910c0c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The senator’s ………………… made him intolerant of other countries.",
            "description": "Chauvinism – super patriotism",
            "answers": [
                "brashness",
                "stupidity",
                "chauvinism"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6d5b966fd29b499a8cc7b19a61b718a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher ………………… the child for arriving late.",
            "description": "To chastise is to punish or scold. All of these words mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "chastised",
                "reprimanded",
                "censured",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "f4cd23fbbd134fee8515e8029da46fa8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Without rules, people would live in a state of ……………….",
            "description": "Chaos – turmoil, upheaval, confusion",
            "answers": [
                "chaos",
                "harmony",
                "bungle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d64239c37a334b03858687789fc78fdf"
        },
        {
            "question": "The minister made a ………………….. denial of the charges that he had taken bribes.",
            "description": "Categorical – absolute, unconditional",
            "answers": [
                "brazen",
                "categorical",
                "brash"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "daedc68fdfbb489e9dd7256ae6db6601"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plumber …………………. the job and now the pipe leaks.",
            "description": "Bungle – do badly, make a mess of",
            "answers": [
                "bungled",
                "abashed",
                "chastised"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5d6328bf473441f48da1b4fc2fa44501"
        },
        {
            "question": "How can you believe such a ………………….. lie?",
            "description": "Brazen – impudent, shameless",
            "answers": [
                "brazen",
                "white",
                "sordid"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "620c58eca07f4bec9e0befc3d5789f76"
        },
        {
            "question": "Buying the house without having it appraised was …………………",
            "description": "Brash – rash, reckless, careless",
            "answers": [
                "brazen",
                "brash",
                "impudent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9c21dd3598a460d922e36e7aebf632d"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is important to ............................. with those in trouble to really understand their suffering.",
            "description": "To empathize is to share the feelings of another person.",
            "answers": [
                "empathize",
                "emote",
                "devise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "913f9fcb9bd34616b5053257b76c189d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The spy checked into the hotel under a ............................ name.",
            "description": "Fictitious - unreal or false",
            "answers": [
                "figurative",
                "fictitious",
                "alien"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b11cbd3d650c40449bb201fa546e55a9"
        }
    ]
}